{
    "question_pool": [
        {
            "question_id": "G1A01",
            "question": "On which HF/MF bands is a General class license holder granted all amateur frequency privileges?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "60 meters, 20 meters, 17 meters, and 12 meters",
                    "B": "160 meters, 80 meters, 40 meters, and 10 meters",
                    "C": "160 meters, 60 meters, 30 meters, 17 meters, 12 meters, and 10 meters",
                    "D": "160 meters, 30 meters, 17 meters, 15 meters, 12 meters, and 10 meters"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A02",
            "question": "On which of the following bands is phone operation prohibited?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "160 meters",
                    "B": "30 meters",
                    "C": "17 meters",
                    "D": "12 meters"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A03",
            "question": "On which of the following bands is image transmission prohibited?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "160 meters",
                    "B": "30 meters",
                    "C": "20 meters",
                    "D": "12 meters"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A04",
            "question": "Which of the following amateur bands is restricted to communication only on specific channels, rather than frequency ranges?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "11 meters",
                    "B": "12 meters",
                    "C": "30 meters",
                    "D": "60 meters"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "D"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A05",
            "question": "Which of the following frequencies is in the General class portion of the 40-meter band in ITU Region 2?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "7.250 MHz",
                    "B": "7.500 MHz",
                    "C": "40.200 MHz",
                    "D": "40.500 MHz"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "A"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A06",
            "question": "Which of the following frequencies is within the General class portion of the 75-meter phone band?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "1875 kHz",
                    "B": "3750 kHz",
                    "C": "3900 kHz",
                    "D": "4005 kHz"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A07",
            "question": "Which of the following frequencies is within the General class portion of the 20-meter phone band?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "14005 kHz",
                    "B": "14105 kHz",
                    "C": "14305 kHz",
                    "D": "14405 kHz"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A08",
            "question": "Which of the following frequencies is within the General class portion of the 80-meter band?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "1855 kHz",
                    "B": "2560 kHz",
                    "C": "3560 kHz",
                    "D": "3650 kHz"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A09",
            "question": "Which of the following frequencies is within the General class portion of the 15-meter band?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "14250 kHz",
                    "B": "18155 kHz",
                    "C": "21300 kHz",
                    "D": "24900 kHz"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A10",
            "question": "Which of the following frequencies is available to a control operator holding a General class license?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "28.020 MHz",
                    "B": "28.350 MHz",
                    "C": "28.550 MHz",
                    "D": "All these choices are correct"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "D"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A11",
            "question": "When General class licensees are not permitted to use the entire voice portion of a band, which portion of the voice segment is generally available to them?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "The lower frequency end",
                    "B": "The upper frequency end",
                    "C": "The lower frequency end on frequencies below 7.3 MHz, and the upper end on frequencies above 14.150 MHz",
                    "D": "The upper frequency end on frequencies below 7.3 MHz, and the lower end on frequencies above 14.150 MHz"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "B"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A12",
            "question": "Which of the following applies when the FCC rules designate the Amateur Service as a secondary user on a band?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "Amateur stations must record the call sign of the primary service station before operating on a frequency assigned to that station",
                    "B": "Amateur stations can use the band only during emergencies",
                    "C": "Amateur stations can use the band only if they do not cause harmful interference to primary users",
                    "D": "Amateur stations may only operate during specific hours of the day, while primary users are permitted 24- hour use of the band"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "C"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A13",
            "question": "What is the appropriate action if, when operating on either the 30-meter or 60-meter bands, a station in the primary service interferes with your contact?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "Notify the FCCs regional Engineer in Charge of the interference",
                    "B": "Increase your transmitter\u2019s power to overcome the interference",
                    "C": "Attempt to contact the station and request that it stop the interference",
                    "D": "Move to a clear frequency or stop transmitting"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "D"
        },
        {
            "question_id": "G1A14",
            "question": "Which of the following may apply in areas under FCC jurisdiction outside of ITU Region 2?",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "A": "Station identification may have to be in a language other than English",
                    "B": "Morse code may not be permitted",
                    "C": "Digital transmission may not be permitted",
                    "D": "Frequency allocations may differ"
                }
            ],
            "right_answer": "D"
        }
    ]
}